Inventory of the Lelan Flor Sillin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Institute of Nuclear Power Operations (INPO) File, 1979-1984
  - Workshops, 1983-1984
    - Board of Directors/Chief Executive Officer (CEO) workshop, 1984 November (Box-folder 41: 6-7, Box-folder 42: 1-2)
    - CEO workshop, 1983 September 22-23 (Box-folder 36: 13, Box-folder 37: 1-3)
    - CEO workshop, executive talk session, 1983 September (Box-folder 35: 4)
    - CEO workshop, follow-up on INPO programs, 1983 September (Box-folder 35: 3)
    - CEO workshop information, 1983 September 24-25 (Box-folder 37: 4)
    - CEO workshop, proceedings of speeches and discussions, 1983 September 22-23 (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - CEO workshop, 1984
      - "Managing Our Industry,", 1984 December (Box-folder 75: 6)
      - Speeches, 1984 November (Box-folder 75: 8-9)
      - 1984 November 29 (Box-folder 75: 10)
    - Chemistry Managers' workshop, 1984 (Box-folder 75: 7)
    - Chemistry workshop, 1983 November 8-9 (Box-folder 36: 10)
    - Emergency Operating Procedures Implementation Assistance workshop, 1983 August 25-26 (Box-folder 35: 5)
    - Emergency Preparedness workshop, 1983 October 6-7 (Box-folder 36: 12)
    - Nuclear Notepad workshop, 1983 June 2-3 (Box-folder 35: 6)
    - Operation Superintendent workshop, 1983 October 24-25 (Box-folder 36: 11)
    - Plant manager's workshop, 1983 May 22-24 (Box-folder 35: 7)
    - Support manager's workshop, 1983 March 29-30 (Box-folder 34: 5)
    - Various workshops, 1984 (Box-folder 76: 5)
  - Presentation to the New York Society of Security Analysts, 1984 June 4 (Box-folder 20: 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous reports and presentations, 1984 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Speeches, 1984 (Box-folder 75: 11)
  - Speech at Cigna, 1984 September 17 (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - Nuclear Utility Task Action Committee (NUTAC), 1983-1984
    - "Control Room Design Analysis Guideline,", 1983 December (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - "Control Room Design Review Survey Development Guideline,", 1984 January 18 (Box-folder 23: 5)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Utility Nuclear Power Oversight Committee, 1983-1984
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 76: 4)
    - Conference calls, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 76: 2-3)
  - Annual report, "Nuclear Professionals Sharing the Commitment,", 1982 (Box-folder 58: 8)
  - Annual report, "Advancing Excellence,", 1983 (Box-folder 58: 7)
  - Annual report, 1984 (Box-folder 42: 7)
  - Budget, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - 1984 Budget
    - Administration, 1983 May-June (Box-folder 38: 6)
    - Analysis and engineering, 1983 June (Box-folder 38: 8)
    - Communications, 1983 June (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - Construction project evaluation, 1983 June (Box-folder 39: 4)
    - Evaluation and assistance, 1983 June (Box-folder 38: 9)
    - International participation, 1983 June (Box-folder 39: 3)
    - Radiological protection and emergency preparedness, 1983 June (Box-folder 39: 1)
    - Summaries, 1983 June (Box-folder 38: 5)
    - Training and education, 1983 June (Box-folder 38: 7)
  - Institutional plan, 1983 (Box-folder 14: 12, Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Goals and objectives, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 14: 11, Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, by-laws, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 84: 7-11)
  - Membership listing, 1982 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Booklets on criteria, guidelines, and reports, 1980-1983 (Box 15)
    - "Assessment of Motor Operated Failures,", 1980 October
    - "Control Room Design Review Implementation Guideline,", 1983 July
    - "Emergency Operating Procedures Generation Package Guideline,", 1983 February
    - "Emergency Operating Procedures Implementation Assistance Program,", 1982 April
    - "Emergency Operating Procedures Implementation Guideline,", 1983 July
    - "Emergency Operating Procedures Validation Guideline,", 1983 March
    - "Performance Objectives and Criteria for Construction Project Evaluations,", 1983 June 22
    - "Nuclear Notepad,", 1983 May
    - "Significant Event Evaluation and Information Network,", 1983 February
  - Construction project evaluations, 1983 (Box-folder 18: 1-3, Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Performance objectives and criteria for corporate evaluations, 1984 January (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Plant evaluations, 1981-1984
    - Evaluation correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 44: 1)
    - Performance objectives and criteria for plant evaluations, 1983 April (Box-folder 44: 2)
    - Team Manager Handbook for Evaluations and Assistance Visits, Volumes I and II, 1982 April-September (Box-folder 44: 3)
    - Arkansas Nuclear One (ANO-1) Generating Station, 1983 August 17 (Box-folder 44: 4)
    - Beaver Valley Power Station, 1983 October (Box-folder 44: 5)
    - Beaver Valley Power Station Unit 2, 1983 May (Box-folder 44: 6)
    - Big Rock Nuclear Plant, 1983 November (Box-folder 44: 7)
    - Browns Ferry Nuclear Plant, 1983 August (Box-folder 44: 8)
    - Brunswick Steam Electric Plant, 1983 (Box-folder 44: 9)
    - Calvert Cliffs Nuclear Power Plant, 1984 February (Box-folder 44: 10)
    - Clinton Power Station, 1983 December (Box-folder 44: 11)
    - D.C. Cook Nuclear Power Plant, 1983 October (Box-folder 44: 12)
    - Connecticut Yankee, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 45: 1-3)
    - Crystal River Nuclear Plant Unit 3, 1983 (Box-folder 45: 4)
    - Duane Arnold Energy Center, 1982 (Box-folder 45: 5)
    - Farley Nuclear Plant, 1983 June 20 (Box-folder 45: 6)
    - FitzPatrick Nuclear Power Station, 1983 November (Box-folder 45: 7)
    - Fort Calhoun Station Unit 1, 1983 October (Box-folder 45: 8)
    - Fort St. Vrain Generating Station, 1983 (Box-folder 45: 9)
    - Robert E. Ginna Nuclear Power Plant, 1983 November (Box-folder 45: 10)
    - Hatch Nuclear Plant, 1983 June 22 (Box-folder 45: 11)
    - Indian Point Station, 1983 May (Box-folder 45: 12)
    - Indian Point Nuclear Power Plant 1982, 1983 April 27 (Box-folder 46: 1)
    - LaSalle County Nuclear Generating Station, 1983 August (Box-folder 46: 2)
    - Limerick Generating Station Units I and II, 1983 July (Box-folder 46: 3)
    - Maine Yankee Atomic Power Plant, 1983 June 1 (Box-folder 46: 4)
    - McGuire Nuclear Station, 1983 June 22 (Box-folder 46: 5)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station Unit 3, 1983 August (Box-folder 46: 6)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station 1982, 1983 March 15 (Box-folder 46: 7)
    - Monticello Nuclear Generating Plant, 1983 May (Box-folder 46: 8)
    - North Anna Power Station, 1983 September (Box-folder 46: 9)
    - Oyster Creek Nuclear Generating Station 1982, 1983 May 3 (Box-folder 46: 10)
    - Palisades Nuclear Plant, 1983 May (Box-folder 46: 11)
    - Pilgrim Nuclear Power Station, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 47: 1)
    - Pilgrim Briefing Book, 1983 October (Box-folder 47: 2-3)
    - Evaluation of Pilgrim Nuclear Power Station, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 47: 4)
    - H.B. Robinson Unit 2, 1983 December (Box-folder 47: 5)
    - Saint Lucie Power Plant 1982, 1983 March 18 (Box-folder 47: 6)
    - San Onofre Nuclear Generating Station Unit 1, 1983 June (Box-folder 47: 7)
    - Seabrook Station, 1983 November (Box-folder 48: 1)
    - South Texas Construction Project Evaluation of the Houston Lighting and Power Company, 1983 September (Box-folder 48: 2)
    - Surry Power Station 1982, 1983 May 10 (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - Susquehanna Stream Electric Station, 1983 September (Box-folder 48: 4)
    - Three Mile Island Nuclear Power Station, 1983 (Box-folder 48: 5)
    - Trojan Nuclear Plant, 1983 September (Box-folder 48: 6)
    - Turkey Point Nuclear Plant, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 48: 7-8)
    - Vermont Yankee Nuclear Power Station, 1983 September (Box-folder 48: 9)
    - Wolf Creek Generating Station, 1983 October (Box-folder 48: 10)
    - Zion Nuclear Generating Station, 1983 June (Box-folder 48: 11)
  - Plant evaluations, 1984 (Box 19-20)
    - Alabama Power Company, December 1984
    - Arkansas Nuclear One, 1984 October
    - Bellefonte Nuclear Plant Units 1 and 2, 1984 March
    - Braidwood Nuclear Power Station, 1984 July
    - Browns Ferry Nuclear Plant, 1984 October
    - Brunswick Steam Electric Plant, 1984 December
    - Cooper Nuclear Station, 1984 July
    - Connecticut Yankee Power Station, 1984 November
    - Crystal River Nuclear Power Plant, 1984 November
    - Davis-Besse Nuclear Power Station, 1984 March
    - Dresden Nuclear Power Station, 1984 February
    - Duane Arnold Energy Center, 1984 May
    - Farley Nuclear Plant, 1984 October
    - Florida Power Corporation, 1984 December
    - Fort St. Vrain Generating Station, 1984 July
    - Hatch Nuclear Plant, 1984 October
    - Hope Creek Generating Station, 1984 July
    - Indian Point Station Unit Number 2, 1982
    - Indian Point 3 Nuclear Plant, 1984 March
    - Kewaunee Nuclear Power Plant, 1984 February
    - La Crosse Boiling Water Reactor, 1984 January
    - Maine Yankee Atomic Power Plant, 1984 October
    - McGuire Nuclear Station, 1984 August
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, 1984 October
    - Nine Mile Point Unit 2, 1984 October
    - Nine Mile Point Nuclear Station, 1984 February
    - Oconee Nuclear Station, 1984 January
    - Oyster Creek Nuclear Generating Station, 1984 November
  - Evaluation reports, 1984
    - Guidelines for Quality Control Inspector and Nondestructive Examination Technician Training, 1984 January (Box-folder 77: 1)
    - Point Beach Nuclear Plant, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 2)
    - Prairie Island Nuclear Generating Plant, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 3)
    - Quad Cities Nuclear Generating Station, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 4)
    - Rancho Seco Nuclear Generating Station Unit 1, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 5)
    - River Bend Station Unit 1, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 6)
    - St. Lucie Power Plant, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 7)
    - Salem Generating Station, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 8)
    - San Onofre Nuclear Generating Station, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 9)
    - Sequoyah Nuclear Plant, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 10)
    - Shearon Harris Nuclear Power Plant, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 11)
    - Surry Power Station, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 12)
    - Three Mile Island Nuclear Power Station Unit 1, 1984 (Box-folder 77: 13)
    - Turkey Point Nuclear Plant, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 1)
    - Virgil C. Summer Nuclear Station, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 2)
    - Vogtle Electric Generating Plant Units 1 and 2, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 3)
    - Yankee Nuclear Power Station, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 4)
    - Zion Nuclear Generating Station, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 5)
  - Significant Event Report and Operations and Maintenance Reminder, 1983
    - First Quarter Report, 1983 April (Box-folder 37: 7)
    - Second Quarter Report, 1983 July 12 (Box-folder 37: 8)
    - Third Quarter Report, 1983 November 2 (Box-folder 37: 9)
    - Significant Event Report and Operations Maintenance Reminder, 1983 (Box-folder 76: 9)
  - Significant Operating Experience Report, 1983 (Box-folder 76: 8)
  - Analysis of root causes in 1983 Significant Event Report, 1984 August (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Westinhouse Gold Medal Award presented to E.P. Wilkinson, 1983 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - E.P. Wilkinson retirement dinner, 1984 March 20 (Box-folder 76: 6)
  - Compensation program, 1983 January (Box-folder 57: 8-9)
  - Scholarship program, 1983 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - Technical instructor training and qualification, 1982 October (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - Pressurized Water Reactor Control Room Operator, Senior Control Room Operator, and Shift Supervisor Qualification, 1983 June (Box-folder 39: 7)
  - General employee training in radiological protection, 1983 March (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Analysis and Engineering Division: Corporate Engineering Support, 1984 September (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Survey of nuclear related occupational employment in US electric utilities, 1982 December (Box-folder 39: 6)
  - Emergency Excercise Management Manual, 1983 August (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - Human Resources Management: A System Description, 1983 (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - Nuclear Network: Users Manual, 1984 April (Box-folder 60: 2)
  - "Foremost Safety and Reliability Issues,", 1984 May 1 (Box 76: 7)
  - Board of Directors' book, 1984 June 14 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Press release, 1983 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Partial itinerary, numbered box 3, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 7)
  - Information packets to Cigna Corporation, 1984 September 17 (Box-folder 76: 10)
  - Nuclear Power Assembly, 1984 March 2-5 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - Palisades Nuclear Plant, 1984 December (Box-folder 85: 1)
  - Peach Bottom Atomic Power Station, 1984 February (Box-folder 85: 2)
  - Perry Nuclear Project, 1984 May (Box-folder 85: 3)
  - Pilgrim Nuclear Power Station, 1984 September (Box-folder 85: 4)
- International Energy Associates Limited File, 1983-1985
  - General correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 75: 1-4, Box-folder 74: 11-13)
  - Advisory Board correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 74: 6-9)
  - Dinner meeting at University Club with Brewer, Gray, and Chipman, 1984 January 18 (Box-folder 74: 2)
  - Meeting at Washington D.C., 1984 February 8 (Box-folder 74: 3)
  - Request for proposal for the appraisal of general office corporate management and Rancho Seco Nuclear Station supervision, 1984 August 30 (Box-folder 74: 4)
  - Prudency audits, 1984 August (Box-folder 74: 10)
  - Newspaper articles, 1984 (Box-folder 74: 5)
- Northeast Utilities (NU) File, 1960-1984
  - General correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 78: 7-8)
  - Correspondence
    - 1969 March-1970 December (Box-folder 2: 8-9, Box-folder 3: 1-8, Box-folder 4: 1-7, Box-folder 5: 1-2)
      Sillin was the president of Northest Utilities at the time of this correspondence.
    - 1971 January-March (Box-folder 96: 8-9)
    - 1971 April-June (Box-folder 94: 5-6)
    - 1971 July-September (Box-folder 95: 1)
    - 1971 August-September (Box-folder 95: 2)
    - 1971 October-December (Box-folder 96: 1, Box-folder 95: 8)
  - Committee on Utilities correspondence, 1984 August-October (Box-folder 51: 9)
  - Member Committee of the United States correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 51: 11)
  - Load Forecasting Methodology Committee, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - Prime Movers committee, 1969 May 5 (Box-folder 73: 13)
  - Materials for NU staff meeting, 1977 May 16 (Box-folder 97: 2)
  - Meeting with Malcolm Black regarding simulator building, 1984 October 11 (Box-folder 51: 8)
  - Ford Foundation, Arlie House Conference, 1970 April-May (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - United States National Committee World Energy Conference, 1984 September 6 (Box-folder 51: 12)
  - New York Superstar Telethon at The Club at Citicorp Center, 1984 October 15 (Box-folder 51: 10)
  - Utility Performance Monitoring reports, 1984 (Box-folder 52: 1-3)
  - Millstone 3 records, 1984
    - "A Diagnostic of Construction to Operation Transition of Millstone 3,", 1984 January (Box-folder 52: 6)
    - Millstone 3 audit, Nielsen-Wurster briefing documents, 1984 October-November (Box-folder 51: 5-6)
    - Millstone 3 executive status reports, 1984 February-March (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - Millstone 3 prudence audit, 1984 (Box-folder 51: 2-3)
    - Millstone 3 prudence reports and documentation, 1984 October-November (Box-folder 51: 4)
    - Millstone 3 related actions, 1984 January (Box-folder 52: 5)
    - Millstone 3 simulator building and training center, 1984 February-October (Box-folder 51: 7)
  - Environment, general, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 30: 6-9)
  - Plant siting, 1969 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Plant siting, 1971 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - Plant siting, Connecticut, regarding Senate Bill 1458, 1971 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - Proxy materials, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 98: 4)
  - Regional and environmental planning, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 30: 2-5)
  - Trustees' questionnaire and conflict of interest statements, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 52: 4)
  - Electric Power Reliability Act, 1969 (Box-folder 78: 9-10)
  - National Power Survey, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 31: 6-12)
  - Federal Power Bar Assocation, 1970 April 30 (Box-folder 73: 14)
  - Congressional bills to amend the Federal Power Act, 1969 December 31 (Box-folder 79: 2)
  - Hearings to amend the Federal Power Act, 1969 December 31 (Box-folder 79: 1)
- Urban America, Inc./Youth Organizations United (YOU) File, 1967-1970
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, memoranda, and miscellaneous documents.
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 98: 1-2)
  - YOU correspondence, 1968-1973
    - 1968 (Box-folder 102: 3)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 96: 2)
    - 1969 January-March (Box-folder 101: 1)
    - 1969 April (Box-folder 100: 2)
    - 1969 May (Box-folder 100: 1)
    - 1969 June-August (Box-folder 99: 2)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 99: 3-4)
    - 1971-1973 (Box-folder 101: 5)
  - Board of Trustees' meetings, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 103: 2-3, Box-folder 1: 1-3, Box-folder 102: 1)
  - Annual meeting, 1968 June 5-7 (Box-folder 103: 4)
  - Annual meeting on May 20, 1969, 1969 January-June (Box-folder 1: 5-8)
    Includes information and documents about Urban America Inc.'s work with Youth Organizations United and their own urbanization project.
  - Finance and Budget Committee meeting information, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 101: 4)
  - Urban Coalition Action Council, 1970 (Box-folder 102: 4)
  - YOU luncheon, 1969 (Box-folder 99: 5)
  - Documents, 1969 (Box-folder 98: 3)
  - Documents for various youth programs, 1969 (Box-folder 103: 1)
  - Documents on urban problems and programs, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 102: 2)
  - Executive Committee documents, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 100: 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous Youth Project documents, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 101: 2-3)
  - Urban Coalition documents and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 99: 1)
  - Publications and descriptions of various urban youth organizations, undated (Box-folder 1: 9-10)
  - Sillin's election as a trustee of Urban America, 1967 April-May (Box-folder 1: 4)
- Wesleyan University File, 1982-1985
  - General correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 12)
  - Board of Trustees' correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 53: 8)
  - Campaign for Liberal Learning correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 54: 6)
  - Financial Planning correspondence, 1984 August (Box-folder 56: 5)
  - Portfolio Subcommittee correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 2)
  - Board of Trustees' meetings, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 53: 1-7)
    These meetings were usually held in the Science Center at the Daniel Woodhead lounge.
  - Campaign for Liberal Learning meetings, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 54: 1-5)
  - Development Committee meetings, 1984 February-July (Box-folder 53: 9-16)
  - Financial Planning Committee meetings, 1984 (Box-folder 56: 6-10)
  - Investment Committee meetings, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 13-15)
  - Portfolio Subcommittee meetings, 1984 February-October (Box-folder 55: 3-7)
  - Annual reports of various university departments, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 54: 7-11)
  - Sabbatical reports, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 55: 8)
  - Wesleyan Alumni Fund, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 52: 7)
  - Challenge Grant, Kresge Foundation, 1983 December 14 (Box-folder 55: 13)
  - Etherington Scholarship, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 10)
  - Appraisals of University Endowment Funds, 1984 (Box-folder 56: 1- 4)
  - Trustee weekend, 1984 April-December (Box-folder 53: 1, Box-folder 52: 8-9)
  - Partial itinerary for Wesleyan documents in collection, numbered Box 16, undated (Box-folder 55: 9)
  - Questionnaires, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 55: 11)
- Other Organizations File, 1962-1973, 1985
  - Americans for Energy Independence, 1985 (Box-folder 73: 18)
  - Charter New York Corporation, 1967 (Box-folder 95: 4)
  - Children's Home of Poughkeepsie, undated (Box-folder 5: 3-9)
  - Fishkill Rotary Club, 1961 April 26 (Box-folder 88: 8)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1973 July (Box-folder 93: 2)
  - Poughkeepsie Rotary Club, 1961 December 6 (Box-folder 88: 9)
  - Public Utilities Commission, 1969 December 17 (Box-folder 88: 11)
  - Quarter Century Club, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 88: 13-16, Box-folder 89: 1-3)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 60: 4)
  - Traveler's Corporation, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 33: 6, Box-folder 34: 1-3, Box-folder 60: 3)
  - Traveler's Executive Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Williams College Center for Environmental Studies, 1968 (Box-folder 62: 9)
  - Working Committee on Utilities, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 70: 11, Box-folder 71: 1-3)
  - Worthington Corporation, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 73: 15-16)
  - Yankee-Dixie Power Association, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 30: 1)